六年前的今天 我妈妈去世了
My mother died six months ago today.
我们在医院得知她得了动脉瘤
At the hospital, they told us she'd had an aneurysm.
我为她做不了什么
There was nothing I could do for her.
我现在已经很擅长伪装自己一切都好
I guess I've gotten pretty good at pretending to be okay.
这破玩意儿坏了吧
I don't think this stupid thing is even working.
你打开了吗
You turn it on?
当然打开了
Of course I turned it on.
你把镜头盖子去掉吗
Did you take the lens cap off?
这样就好了
Yeah, that probably would help.
Phoebe 你能...
Okay, Phoebe, can you just...
好的
Okay.
准备好了吗
Ready?
开拍
Rolling, and action.
视频日记 第18天
Video Diary, day 18.
今天是非常重要的一天
Now, today is an extremely important day.
为什么
Why?
因为这是我给芝加哥大学的申请资料
Because here is my application to the University of Chicago,
我希望秋天的时候去芝加哥大学学习古希腊古罗马文学
where I'm hoping to study Classics in the fall.
你有听说过网络吗
Have you ever heard of the Internet?
我知道现如今都是在网上提交申请
I know nowadays you can submit this stuff online,
但是我个人更喜欢传统的方式
but personally, I prefer the more traditional route.
你也看到了 这个信封非常厚
As you can see, this envelope is seriously thick.
为什么呢
Why is that?
申请表上的第七个问题是
Well, question seven on the application asks you
说说你的优点和缺点
to tell them what your best and worst qualities are,
但是3.5英寸的空间
but they only give you three-and-a-half inches.
addy 看路
Addy, watch the road.
纸张上只有3.5英寸的空间
Three-and-a-half inches on a page.
抱歉 但是我的缺点好多的
I'm sorry, but my worst qualities took up a lot more
那点儿地方根本不够
than three-and-a-half inches.
所以我就决定增加几页
So I decided to throw in a few extra pages.
你增加了多少
How many?
-整整22页  -哇
-Twenty-two to be exact. -Wow!
-我知道可能有点过分了  -没错
-I realize that might seem a bit excessive. -It does.
但是 那3.5英寸的空间太小了
However, how are you expected
根本就不够表达自我
to express the very essence of your being
这个世界这么疯狂 那点儿空间
and your views on how insanely crazy this world is
根本不够写
in such a tiny space on a page?
-太疯狂了  -好了 addy 闭嘴吧
-I mean, it's absurd. -Okay, Addy, shut up already.
那有个邮箱
There's a mailbox right there.
太棒了
Great.
Phoebe 你能拍下来这个吗
Phoebe? Can you please film this?
你有在拍吗
You're on me, right?
是的
Right.
这就是我们一直在等待的时刻
And now the moment we've all been waiting for.
我知道你对这一刻是很激动的 Phoebe
I know it's a moment you're very excited about, Phoebe.
没错吧
You're very excited about this, aren't you?
我只想去买咖啡啊
I'm excited to get some coffee.
放邮箱里了
Just put it in the box already.
好了 给我相机
Okay, give me the camera.
天哪 他还没完事儿
Oh, Jesus, he's still not done.
开始吧
Do it.
让开
Hey! Move it!
知道吗
You know what?
我不是很担心增加的那么多页
No. I'm not too worried about the extra pages
因为古罗马诗人维吉尔不是说过吗
because wasn't it Virgil who said,
"勇者得财"
"Fortune sides with him who dares"?
或者更恰当的说法是 大卫 鲍伊的不朽名言
Or perhaps even more apropos are the immortal words of David Bowie,
我不知道我将去往哪里
"I don't know where I'm going from here,
但是我保证旅途不会舞曲
"but I promise it won't be boring."
招生人员才不会读你那22页的东西呢 Addison
They're never going to read 22 extra pages, Addison.
我们没有早早地进入耶鲁大学 Phoebe
Well, for those of us who didn't get into Yale early, Phoebe,
所以当然要更努力一点
we have to put in a little extra effort.
两中杯美式咖啡
Two medium Americanos.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
去你的 Brandon
Add... Screw you, Brandon.
你真的要跟这家伙在一起吗
Are you seriously with this guy?
你真的觉得我在乎你怎么想吗
Do you seriously imagine I give a shit what you think?
但是整个学校的人都觉得你疯了 居然...
Yeah, but the whole school thinks you lost your mind, so...
-Kevin 两中杯美式咖啡  -好的
-Hey, Kevin, two medium Americanos. -Got it.
-你要付钱吗  -不
-Are you going to pay for that? -Nope.
addison的两中杯美式咖啡马上好
Two medium Americanos for Addison coming right up.
-你好啊 兄弟  -你好啊
-What's going on, brother? -How you doing, man?
-很高兴见到你  -很高兴见到你
-Good to see you, man. -Good to see you.
-你读了吗  -嗯
-Did you read it, yet? -Oh!
什么 你怎么这么快
What? Dude, how are you so fast?
我不懂 你怎么想
I don't understand. What did you think?
等你把詹姆斯 鲍德温的书读了以后我们再说
We'll talk about it after you've read the James Baldwin.
拜托 老兄 我没有你那么快啦
Come on, man. I'm not as fast as you.
你们俩初吻过了吗
Oh... Have you guys had your first kiss yet?
还没有 我还在等
No, I'm waiting.
-是哦  -你真应该看看他
-Of course you would. -You should've seen this guy
前几天在哲学课上的表现
in philosophy class the other day,
他怼得Keneally老师哑口无言 太不可思议了
he nailed Miss Keneally to the wall. It was incredible.
-为什么  -因为她在讲什么
-Why? -Because she was giving a stupid lecture
学生为什么翘课
about why students cut class.
然后他回了一句 "就因为你 学生才翘课"
And he said, "You're the reason why students cut class."
-Kevin  -不 我说的是
-Kevin. -No. I said,
"Keneally老师那样的人就是学生翘课的原因"
"People like Miss Keneally are the reason kids cut class."
我开玩笑的
I was joking obviously.
他不是开玩笑 太大胆了
He wasn't joking. It was incredible.
不 她就是整个教育系统的毛病所在
No, she is what's wrong with the education system.
-老兄 我还得工作 好吗  -好的 好的
-Dude, I got to work. Okay? -Okay. Okay.
谢谢 很高兴见到你 Phoebe
Thank you. Good to see you, Phoebs.
好的
You got it.
Kevin 你敢为大家说话 好样的
You stand up for the people, Kevin. You're a good man.
-给你 好的  -谢谢*
-Here you go. Sure. -Thanks.
Phoebe
Phoebe?
-嗯 怎么了  -他怎么样
-Huh? What's up? -How's he doing?
他挺好的
He's okay.
那稍后见
I'll see you later.
好冷
It's chilly.
-我能问你点东西吗  -嗯
-Can I ask you something? -Mmm?
我感觉你跟我在一起
I feel like you hanging out with me has, like,
不利于你跟学校里那些酷家伙的关系
a detrimental effect on your standing with the cool kids.
我们总是一起玩的 addison
We've always hung out, Addison.
不是的 我们从八年级才开始在一起
Not really. I mean, we haven't really since eighth grade.
我之前都像是隐形的*
I sort of went invisible there for a while.
好的 那也许是我发现高中的男生
Okay. Well, maybe it's because I find every guy in high school
全都无聊 太容易看透
to be completely dull and predictable.
为什么
And why is that?
他们太容易看透是因为他们只想跟你交往吗
Are they predictable because they want to hook up?
能听点音乐什么的吗
Can we just get some music or something?
等等 等等
Wait. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
我感觉你把我当中性人
I feel like you see me as somehow sexually neutral
中性这个词源于拉丁文 就是没有睾丸的意思
from the Latin "neuter," as in, without testicles.
我没有那样想你啦
No, I don't see you that way.
很抱歉告诉你 Phoebe
I hate to break it to you, Phoebe.
我不想让你失望
I don't want to disappoint you.
但是你猜怎么着
But guess what?
我想要的和其他人一样
I want what all the other guys want, too.
可以啊
That's okay.
真的吗
Really?
其实
Actually,
我最近也一直在想这个
I've been thinking about this a lot lately.
现在可能也是时候告诉你了
And I guess now is as good a time as any to tell you.
我不想上大学的时候还是个...
I don't want to go off to college as a...
什么
As a what?
就是没有...
Without having, you know,
做啦
done it.
做什么
Done what?
去你的 addison
Screw you, Addison.
我想赶紧完事儿
I wanna get it over with.
好吗 我想跟一个让我觉得安全的人做
All right? I want to have sex with a guy who I feel safe around.
就是不会评判我的人
You know? Who won't judge me.
而且也是个处男
And who is definitely a virgin, too.
你是说我吗
You're talking about me?
等等 什么 你为什么觉得我是处男
Wait, what? What makes you think that I'm a virgin?
addison 闭嘴
Addison, shut up.
我妈妈要跟商务部长开会 直到六点
So, my mom is in a meeting with the Secretary of Commerce until 6:00 p.m.
-你想现在就做  -是的
-You want to do this right now? -Yeah.
在你妈妈跟商务部长开会的时候 商务部长
While there's a meeting between your mom and the Secretary of Commerce?
addison 我发誓 你要是再问的话
Addison, I swear to God, if you ask me another question,
-我就改主意了  -好的好的
-I'm gonna change my mind. -Okay, okay, okay.
你觉得我们应该亲吻吗
Do you think we should kiss?
我觉得我们应该亲吻
I think we should kiss.
好的
Okay.
给你
Here.
-该死 小心  -抱歉
-Shit! Be careful. -Sorry.
好的
Okay.
好了
There.
好的 所以
Okay. So...
就是这样 对吗
That's what this whole thing is about, right?
就这样吗
There? That's all you're gonna say?
好了 我把自己献给你了
There? I just gave myself to you.
好了
There.
我应该继续吗
Should I keep going?
当然
Sure.
-确定  -嗯
-Sure? -Yeah?
嗯
Yeah?
好的
Okay.
-我能继续吻你吗  -好的
-Can I keep kissing you? -Okay.
不知道你是否可以
Yeah, I wonder if you can.
我儿子在用我的旧摄影机拍东西
My son is making a film with my old video camera
他只剩下一条带子了
and he only has one tape left.
你的网站上说你们新旧机器都卖
And your website says that you sell new old ones, so to speak.
是的 就那种型号 60分钟
Yeah, VHS-Cs. Sixty minutes.
好的 我等着
Yeah, I'll hold.
这里是七星面包店 我们在这里为您发回报道
We're here at the Seven Stars Bakery, and as you can tell,
这是犯罪现场
it is a very active crime scene.
我们现在只知道一人死亡
And what we've learned is that at least one person has died.
我们会继续为您带来
We'll continue to bring you information
最新的信息和细节
and details as it becomes available.
现在大家都在热议
Now, there has been significant discussion
这是否和黑帮有关
about whether or not this could be gang related.
你觉得怎么样
So, what do you think?
那还算可以吧
That was okay, right?
嗯 那是...我迄今为止最好的性爱体验
Yeah. I mean, that... That's gotta be some of the best sex I've ever had.
真不敢相信我们刚刚做了
I can't believe we just did that.
是的
Yeah.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我感觉...
You know, I feel like...
自己已经打开了一个非常重要的盒子
I feel like I just checked a really important box.
我感觉我在盒子里发现了大宝贝
I feel like I just checkmated it.
什么声音
What's that noise?
-是我的寻呼机  -哦
-I think it's my pager. -Oh...
好了 你最好看一下
Okay. You should probably get that.
真不敢相信你还用那东西
I can't believe you still actually use that thing.
我爸爸 我能用用你家电话吗
My dad. Can I use your landline?
当然
Yeah, sure.
我妈妈打来的
My mom's calling me.
天哪 她工作期间从不打电话的
Oh, God, she never calls from work.
-她是知道了吗  -太奇怪了吧
-Do you think she knows? -That's weird.
我对天发誓 她对这种事情第六感很强的
I swear to God, she has a sixth sense about this stuff.
喂
Hello?
嗯
Yeah.
等等 妈妈 慢点 怎么了
Wait, wait. Mom, slow down. What?
七星面包店发生了枪击案
There was a shooting at Seven Stars.
一个叫Kevin Broadus被杀
A kid named Kevin Broadus was killed.
天哪 什么时候的事
Oh, my God. When?
发生了什么
What happened?
是Kevin
It's Kevin.
肯尼迪高中学生Kevin Broadus
Kennedy High School student Kevin Broadus
被一名不明身份的袭击者枪杀
was gunned down today by an unidentified assailant.
...他骑红色本田摩托车抵达犯罪现场
...fled the scene of the crime on a red Honda motorcycle.
嫌犯只瞄准一人 没有财务损失
Only one person was targeted. No money was stolen.
这有帮派枪击的迹象
This has all the hallmarks of a gang killing.
我们现在来到
We're gonna take you now live
市区警局发布会现场
to the Metro Police press conference,
Thompson警探正在接受提问
where Detective Thompson is taking questions.
现在下结论太早 我们还没有排除任何可能
Still very early at this point. We're not ruling anything out.
谢谢各位 我们有进一步消息后会通知媒体 谢谢
Thank you all. We'll be with you when we have more information. Thank you.
抱歉 请问 Thompson警探在这里吗
Excuse me. Excuse me. Do you know if Detective Thompson's here?
他刚刚走了
No, I think he just left.
-他们知道是谁干的吗  -应该不知道
-Do they have any idea who did it? -I doubt it.
那些家伙总是团结一致
You know, these guys usually tend to close ranks.
谁 哪些家伙
Who? Which guys?
就是他所在的帮派
Whatever gang he's in.
他们肯定会把凶手藏起来 等风浪过了
They'll just hide him until no one cares anymore.
为什么大家都说这跟帮派有关
Why is everyone saying this is a gang thing?
这里可是特区
It's D.C.
Addison
Addison!
Addison 你为什么不回我电话
Addison, why the hell didn't you call me back?
我呼了你两次
I paged you twice.
出事了
Something happened.
我知道出了什么事
I know what happened.
新闻上都在播 我知道你经常去那里
It's all over the news. And I know you go to that place.
怎么了
What?
他是你朋友吗
Was he a friend of yours?
不
Oh, no.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
儿子 我很抱歉
Son. I'm sorry.
我要...我要上床睡了
I'm just gonna... I'm just gonna go to bed.
好的
Okay.
我们的社区
This is a community and neighborhood
关心17岁孩子被杀一事
that is concerned about the killing of a 17-year-old.
这个社区的人也请放心
Well, this community should know they can rest assured
市区警方正在
that the Metro D.C. Police Department
尽全力找出凶手
is doing everything in our power to find the people who did this.
-我们一定会找到他的  -Phoebe
-And we will find them. -Phoebe?
宝贝儿 准备好了吗
Honey? You almost ready?
我该送你去学校了
I thought I'd take you to school.
不用 我可以自己开车去 没事的
No. I can... I can drive myself. It's fine.
-拜托  -妈妈 开着电视吧 拜托了
-Just, please. -Mom, can you leave it on? Please?
不 那太...你总是看这个对你不好
No. It's really... It's not good for you to obsess about this.
我没有总是看
I'm not obsessing.
听着 我昨晚给Denise打过电话了 我们都同意
Listen, I called Denise last night, and we both agreed
你应该去见见她 就几次 那样会...
that you should see her for just a couple of sessions, that it would be...
妈妈 你反应过度了 别说了
Mom, you're overreacting. Just drop it.
我没有反应过度
I'm not overreacting.
那是非常有创伤的的经历
I just think it's a very traumatic experience
-你需要...  -我没有心理创伤
-and I think that you need to... -I'm not traumatized.
我有 我有心理创伤
Well, I am! I'm traumatized.
给她电话 好吧
Just call her! Okay?
我经历过这一切
I've had experience in this, you know?
我痛苦地发现
I've learned the hard way
人真的没有办法假装这一切没有发生
that you really can't pretend that this never happened.
你得跟人聊聊
You need to talk to somebody.
而且 很明显
And, clearly,
你不想跟我聊
you don't want it to be me.
Addy
Addy.
嗯
Yeah.
早
Hey. Morning.
爸爸
Hey, Dad.
如果你今天想待家里 也可以的
If you want to stay home today, it's okay.
我懂的
You know, I get it.
不 没关系 我去
No, it's fine. I'm going in.
那我开车送你吧
Well, then, why don't I drive you?
不用 我可以自己开车
No, I can drive myself.
你没事吧
You... You all right?
有事 但是...
Not really, but...
想聊聊吗
You want to talk about it?
不想
No.
对了 这个谢谢了
Thanks for this, by the way.
嗯 很高兴你能用上它
Oh, yeah. I'm glad you could find a use for it.
我找到那个盒子的时候
You know, when I pulled it out of the box,
发现了很多你小时候的录影
I found all this footage of you, you know, when you were little.
我们三个
The three of us.
你有时间可以看看
Probably take a look at it sometime.
好的 我不想迟到 所以...
All right, well, I don't want to be late, so...
好的
All right.
好了 爸爸
All right, Dad.
小心点
Take it easy.
爱你
Love you.
心理咨询师全天都在
Grief counselors will be available throughout the day.
认识Kevin Broadus的同学
For those of you who knew Kevin Broadus,
请到一楼
please proceed to the first floor,
接受警方的问话
where the police are taking statements.
请进
Go on in.
在枪击发生前 你有发现
Did you notice anything out of the ordinary
咖啡店里面或外面有什么异常吗
inside or outside the coffee shop before the shooting?
没有
Um, no.
-你还有什么想告诉我们吗  -是的
-Is there anything else you can tell us? -Yes.
Kevin Broadus不是黑帮成员
Kevin Broadus was not in a gang.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
如果你了解Kevin 就会知道他不是
Well, if you knew Kevin, you would know he wasn't in a gang.
他写诗 收藏书 参加爵士乐队
He wrote poetry, collected books, he was in the jazz band.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
你全都记下来了吗
Um, did you get all that?
谢谢你的时间
We appreciate your time.
请叫下一个同学进来
Will you please send the next person in?
我能跟Thompson警探谈谈吗
Uh, can I speak with Detective Thompson?
他现在不在
He's not available right now,
但是如果你想起了什么 请随时跟我们联系
but if you remember anything, you should get in touch with us.
我会回家
I'll be going home
看到阳光 看到太阳
See the light, see the sun
我要回家
I'm just going home
我们昨晚应该都没怎么睡着
I don't suppose any of us got much sleep last night.
跟大家一样
Like most of you probably,
我也流泪
I wept a little,
祷告
I prayed a little.
老师们会怀念Kevin的勤奋
Kevin will be missed by the teachers for his diligence.
爵士乐队也会怀念他
He will be missed by the jazz band,
他是一名优秀的长号手
who is short one excellent trombone player.
-是小号* 虽然都是铜管乐器  -是很多人的朋友
-Trumpet, but it's all brass. -A dear friend to many of you.
当然 最怀念他的肯定是他的父母
Mostly, he'll be missed by his loving parents.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
校长 很抱歉
Sir! I'm really sorry.
我不是想无礼或打断您
I didn't mean to be disrespectful or interrupt,
但是我有话要说
but I just had to say something
-很重要的  -addison
-that's really important. -Addison.
昨天 在事情发生之前 我在咖啡店见过Kevin
I saw Kevin at the coffee shop yesterday right before it happened.
其实 我和Phoebe都见过他
Actually, Phoebe and I both did.
听到新闻之后 我返回了咖啡店
And then after I heard the news, I went back to coffee shop,
那里的新闻人说
and one of the news crew guys told me that
他们会把整个故事写成是帮派仇杀
they're going to write this whole thing off as a gang killing.
也就是说警方可能跟不会追查凶手
Which means they probably won't even go after the guy who did it
因为他们真正破案的几率
because there's such a small chance
非常非常小
of them actually solving the case.
addison 请你坐下
Addison, could you sit down please?
凡是认识Kevin的人都会知道他不是黑帮的
I mean, if anyone here knew Kevin, they knew he wasn't in a gang.
addison 请坐 够了
Addison, please, enough.
我们应该好好谈谈这个
I think this is something we should talk about.
-为什么只有我为Kevin说话  -addison 够了
-Why am I the only one saying anything? -Addison, please.
我已经礼貌地请你坐下了 坐下
I've asked you politely. Sit down!
没人在乎吗
Does no one care?
我会认真听你说完 在我的办公室
I want to hear everything you have to say, in my office!
好吧
All right. Okay.
稍后去找我
See me later.
我们的心情很悲痛
Our emotions are raw.
在座的各位都很受伤
Everybody in this room is hurting.
你干什么啊
Really?
尊重是很重要的
Respect is important.
你怎么回事
So what's going on with you?
你什么意思 校长
What do you mean, sir?
听着 你最近的行为和态度
Look, there has been a marked deterioration of your behavior
有明显的恶化
and your attitude lately.
你还好吗
How are you doing?
我很好
I'm fine.
失去母亲是会造成重大打击 addison
Loss of a parent is a big deal, Addison.
这事和我妈妈无关 校长
This has nothing to do with my mother, sir.
好的
All right.
我建议你这么做...
Here's what I suggest you do.
别再那样找事儿
Cut the theatrics.
让警察去破案
Let the police do their job.
你就好好学习
And you work your ass off.
让你妈妈骄傲
Make your mother proud.
我会去跟芝加哥大学谈
And I'll talk to Chicago.
告诉他们你是学校的宝贵资产
Tell them what an asset you are to the school.
-不允许拍摄 关掉  -好的
-Hey, no cameras in here. Turn it off. -Sure.
我来找Thompson探长
I'm here to see Detective Thompson.
我还能看到红灯呢
I still see the red light.
马上关掉
Turn it off now.
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
有预约吗
You have an appointment?
没有 但是我需要跟他谈谈
Not particularly, but I need to speak with him.
他现在非常忙
He's very busy right now.
好的 那我等着 好吧
Okay. I'm going to wait, all right?
警探
Hi, Detective.
你就是那个拿相机的孩子
So you're the kid with the camera.
是的
Yeah, that's right.
我们收到你的消息了
We've got your statement.
你说要补充信息
I understand that there's something that you'd like to add.
是的 你们知道Kevin Broadus不是黑帮的 对吧
Yeah. Um, you guys know that Kevin Broadus was not in a gang, right?
我们不知道
We don't know that.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
嗯 我去过...
Um, well, I mean, I went to...
我跟他做朋友很久了
You know, I've been friends with him for a while,
我知道他不是黑帮的
and I know that he wasn't in a gang.
谁跟你们说他是黑帮成员的
Who told you that he was in a gang?
你不是说有信息要补充吗
I thought you came here to tell us something.
我来...只是想...我需要知道到底怎么回事
I mean, I am here... I just... I need to know what's going on.
我没时间搭理你 你来处理吧
I don't have time for this. Could you deal with this kid?
-好的  -长官 拜托了
-Yeah, I got it. -Please sir, listen!
我朋友刚刚被杀
My friend just got killed.
你不能让我干坐着 什么也不做
And you can't expect me just to sit around and not do anything about it, okay?
听着 孩子 我知道他是你朋友
Listen, son. I know he was your friend,
相信我 我们也像你一样 想赶紧抓住凶手
and believe me, we want to catch whoever did this just as much as you do,
但是现在 我们要处理辖区内的24起谋杀
but right now, we're dealing with 24 homicides in this district alone,
这还仅仅是过去两周发生的事
and that's just in the past two weeks.
抱歉 但是如果你没有新信息要补充
I'm sorry, but if you don't have anything new to tell us,
我要回去工作了
I have to get back to work.
别太激动
Take it easy now.
我在找你
I was looking for you.
你还好吗
You okay?
嗯 我没事
Yeah, I'm all right.
你想谈谈吗 或者...
Do you want to talk about it? Or...
警方已经下定决心了
The police have already made up their minds.
什么
What?
你可不知道
You don't know that.
Phoebe 前一秒我们还在跟他说话
Listen, Phoebe, one second we were talking to him,
后一秒他就走了 这完全讲不通啊
and the next he's gone. It just doesn't make any sense.
大家都继续各自生活 好像什么都没有发生一样
Everyone is just moving on like nothing happened.
addy
Addy.
必须有人做点什么
Someone needs to do something.
addy 我知道你妈妈的事情后...
Addy, I know after what happened with your mom...
有时候...
You know, sometimes
坏事就那样发生了 就是那样而已 addy
bad things, I don't know, Addy, they just happen.
Phoebe 真深刻啊
Phoebe. That's really deep.
我感觉好多了 谢谢你
I feel so much better. Thank you.
addison 我只是想帮你而已
Addison. I'm just trying to help you.
Addison
Addison?
嗨
Hi.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
嗯
Yeah.
Venderleun先生需要炭粉
Mr. Venderleun needs toner.
又要
Again?
你等一下
You wait here.
好的
Okay.
你告诉Venderleun这些东西
You tell Mr. Venderleun from me that these resources
是供全学校的 不是只给他的班用的
are for the entire school and not just for his class.
好 我会的 非常感谢
Okay, I will. Thank you so much.
上车 我有东西给你看
Hey! Hey, there's something... There's something I gotta show you.
我一会儿就要上汉语课了
I have Mandarin in, like, five minutes.
-汉语 别去了 这很重要的  -不行
-Mandarin? No. This is really important. -Yes. Look, I can't.
我上次翘课 为了跟你睡
I skipped it last time so I could sleep with you.
-今天必须得去了  -上车啦
-So I have to do it today. -Come on!
听着 这是Strauss女士的记录
Look. This is from Mrs. Strauss.
Kevin有情绪困扰的征兆
"Kevin has begun to show signs of emotional trouble.
他最近的成绩下滑也表明
"The recent slide in academic results suggest
他可能在经历一些重大的情感困难
"he may be dealing with significant emotional difficulties
在校外
"outside of school,
但是他不愿意在心理咨询室细说
"which he is reluctant to elaborate upon in our sessions."
天哪 addison
Christ, Addison.
你觉得这意味着什么
What do you think that means?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得我得跟Strauss聊聊
I think I should talk to Strauss.
说什么
And say what?
我偷了你的资料
"Hi, I stole your file,
希望你能给我详细解释一下
"and, you know, I would love if you could talk me through it"?
不 显然不是 但是这可能会带领我们发现一些东西
No, obviously not, but I think this could lead to something.
如果我们能弄清楚这一切呢
What if we could figure this out?
你在乎吗
Don't you even care?
这不是问题的重点
That's not what this is about.
Phoebe 拜托 我们...得...
Phoebe. Come on. We... Like...
我今天在体育馆外看到你贴的单子了
I saw your posters today outside of the gym.
-我把它们扯下来了  -什么 为什么
-I tore them down. -What? Why?
因为大家都在取笑你
'Cause, Addison, everyone's making fun of you.
-他们知道是你干的  -所以你因为我觉得很丢脸
-They know it's you. -So you're embarrassed by me?
不是啦 我没有
No, I'm not embarrassed by you.
可以跟我做爱
It's okay to have sex with me,
-但是却不让别人知道我们是朋友  -当然不是了
-but you don't want people to know we're friends? -Of course not!
我们当然是朋友
I mean, of course it's okay that we're friends.
听着 如果你觉得我丢脸 那就告诉我啊
Listen, if you're ashamed of me, just tell me, okay?
不是的 笨蛋
No, you idiot!
我觉得丢脸的是 虽然你很蠢
I did it because of in spite of how stupid you're being,
可我还是在乎你
I actually give a shit about you.
我能用用你的手机吗 这可能是线索
Um, can I borrow your phone? This could be a lead.
天哪
Jesus Christ.
快啦 让我用用你的手机
Come on! Let me borrow your phone.
-喂  -喂
-Hello? -Hello.
Addison
Addison?
Addis...
-谁啊  -不知道 他挂断了
-Who was it? -I don't know. They hung up.
Addison 你好像没明白 我也在经历这一切
Addison, you don't seem to realize that I'm going through this, too.
我也一直在想这事 但是...
And I can't stop thinking about it either, okay? But...
这事跟你无关
It's not about you.
你也无力改变什么
And there's nothing you can do to change it, okay?
我上课要迟到了 我得走了
Now I'm late for class. I gotta go.
你好 这里是Schacht一家
Hi, you've reached the Schacht family,
Sarah Theo和Addison
Sarah, Theo and Addison.
我们现在无法接电话
We can't come to the phone right now.
请留言 我们会尽快回电
So leave us a message, and we'll get back to you as soon as we can.
喂 我是肯尼迪高中的Karlstadt校长
Uh, hello. This is Principal Karlstadt at Robert Kennedy High.
如果可以 请明天8点30来一趟我办公室
I would like, if you can, for you to come in tomorrow at 8:30 into my office.
是紧急事件
It's a matter of some urgency.
家长和孩子就应该多联系
Parents and children should be in touch with each other.
我们有联系啊
We are in touch with each other.
用寻呼机联系
Through a pager.
他用我女儿的电话打电话
Except, he had to use my daughter's phone to call...
孩子都经常借电话用的
All kids borrow each other's phone all the time, don't they?
-他没有手机吗  -没有 怎么了
-He doesn't have a cell phone? -No. Is that a problem?
你为什么不给他买手机
Why didn't you get him a cell phone?
冷静 冷静
Okay, let's all calm down. Let's stay very calm.
我的意思是这...
It's not a problem. It's a matter of...
-是安全问题  -冷静 好吗
-It's a safety issue. -Could we calm down please?
我只是在想弄清楚这一切
I'm just trying to make sense of this.
他儿子愣生生地
So, his son has put himself
把自己扯进一桩谋杀案里
smack dab in the middle of a murder case.
-对吗  -嗯...
-Am I right? -Well...
我儿子是个好孩子 我可以这么说吗
Listen, my son is a good kid. Can I just say that?
他去年经历了太多事
I mean, he's been through a lot this last year.
是
Yes.
他失去了母亲 现在又失去了朋友
He's lost his mother and now he's lost a friend.
我的意思是 他只是想帮忙
What I'm trying to say is that I think he's just trying to help.
是 我不会让他儿子
Right. I am not gonna let his kid
威胁到我女儿的生命安全
jeopardize my daughter's life,
或是她的未来
nor her future for that matter.
好了 我们别说了
Okay. I'm gonna stop us right here.
现在是非常非常不稳定的时刻
This is a very, very precarious time for all of us.
我希望你们在跟孩子谈话的时候
So I'd like you to keep that in mind
谨记这一点
when you discuss this with your children.
好的 当然
Yes. Of course.
谢谢您找我们来 校长先生
Thank... Thank you for the meeting, Mr. Karlstadt.
很受教育 谢谢
It's been very educational. Thank you.
等你们跟孩子们聊过之后我再跟你们谈谈
Okay, I'll speak to you again after you talk to your children.
非常感谢 我今晚就跟他谈
Thank you very much. I'll talk with him tonight.
-嗨 美女  -嗨
-Hi, beautiful. -Hi.
你还好吗
You doing okay?
嗯 我没事
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
你那个混蛋男友是怎么回事
Um, so, what's up with your asshole boyfriend?
只是我听说了一些奇怪的事
It's just that I heard some weird stuff, that's all.
你想聊聊吗
Do you want to talk about it?
不 不用了
No. Not really.
哦 好的
Oh... Okay.
-Hi. -Hey.
Uh, could I have a word with you?
Yeah, what's up?
Can I talk to you in private?
Yeah. Sure. Um...
Hey, Alex, will you just watch my stuff? I'll be right back.
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
I kind of wanted your advice.
Yeah?
Something to do with Kevin.
Yeah. Um...
I was in the coffee shop when it happened.
-Really? -Yeah.
I saw something, and I don't know if I should tell Addison.
Tell him what?
Addison.
Mrs. Strauss. Do you have a minute?
Sure. Come in.
The guy who killed Kevin was white.
I saw his wrist when he pushed the door open.
I know something was going on with Kevin before he died.
And I heard that you and him were talking
because he was going through some emotional difficulties.
So, what do you think it means?
I don't know, but I told the cops,
but I don't think they're looking in the right place.
Why?
I mean, I heard Kevin was hanging out with that kid Noel.
-Noel? -Yeah.
And I know he's mixed up with some heavy people.
They're dangerous.
What we talked about was confidential.
Just like the conversation we're having right now is confidential.
Yeah, of course.
But I just want to know if there's anything,
you know, if you had any idea of what was going on with him.
Addison, if you want to talk about how you feel about what's happened,
we can do that.
No, I'm all right. Thank you.
Look, just promise me you won't tell any of this to Addison.
Just not right now, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
-Thanks, Bo. -Yeah. I'll see you.
Yeah.
I was at your school today.
And I was catching a lot of shit about you.
About this.
What's up with this, hmm?
What's going on?
Addison?
Remember that day
that Kevin was killed?
Yeah.
I drove back to the coffee shop after it happened.
That's why I didn't call you.
Okay.
And I...
I saw his body.
Yeah, I saw Kevin. Like, I saw them wheel him out.
Here's this kid.
He gets murdered,
and no one cares.
That's not true, Addy. You know that's not true.
No, it is! That's what it seems like.
People care. They do. They just...
Will you just do me a favor?
Just stop this nonsense. This is... This is crazy, Addison.
It's not nonsense. I'm just trying to do something good.
Yeah, I... I understand, I think I do, what you're trying to do.
But this is a murder investigation.
You don't know what could happen.
Nothing's gonna happen!
Well, I couldn't take it if anything did happen to you.
Just...
If you can't do it for me,
do it for her.
All right?
Yeah.
Video Diary. Day 23.
I don't know, maybe my dad's right.
Maybe I'm not thinking straight.
Maybe I shouldn't forget about the rest of my life.
Phoebe!
Hey.
What's up?
Hi.
What?
Look. So, I know the other night was purely a practical thing for you.
And, you know, I have nothing to compare it to,
except for maybe porn and stuff.
But I just have to say
that it really was sensational,
in the original meaning of the word.
And I have a strong and overwhelming desire
to do it again.
That's bad, huh?
Well, you know,
when I woke up this morning, I...
I looked over at the pillow where your head had been.
Uh...
And I...
And I kind of wished it was still there.
I don't know, we're probably
-just romanticizing it. -Romanticizing it. Yeah. That's classic.
But, uh...
Maybe if we did it again...
What? It might break the spell?
That works.
-Should we... -Yeah.
Okay.
Are you sure your dad's not home?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm sure.
He's out shooting bridges for a Belgian tourist brochure.
Long way from the Washington Post, huh?
What?
That... That was pretty good. Right?
I mean, what do you think?
Better, same?
Worse?
Not worse, but...
Okay.
I mean, the spell is definitely broken.
Yeah.
Really?
No, Addy.
I want you to hold me.
Is it just a one-time thing? I mean, like...
I mean, if we do do this again, which I hope we will,
I mean, like, do you want to usually do the holding afterwards or beforehand?
Usually afterwards, I'm guessing. That's good.
I'm just curious, you know.
-I want to be... -Shut up.
Okay.
Okay. Um...
So, what? I guess we just keep...
We keep doing this until the feeling wears off?
Yeah. Yeah, I'll call you.
Okay.
How are you getting home?
I'm gonna grab a cab. Don't worry about it. It's fine, okay?
Hi.
Hey.
I brought dinner.
Um, I already ate actually, but thank you.
Okay.
How was your trip?
Good.
How was class?
Fine.
I learned five more ways to say "hello."
It was eventful.
Should we talk about Addison Schacht?
Wow!
-You really have people everywhere, huh? -Really?
Addison Schacht. Okay.
What?
What's the problem?
We moved up the hill and they moved down.
I went in to your school yesterday,
and I had a meeting with Karlstadt.
He told me about Addison's so-called "investigation"
into the Broadus murder and your involvement in it.
I'm not involved in it.
He's a friend of mine. That's it.
So he's just a friend, huh?
What does it matter?
What do you have against him?
It's not his fault that his life has been so shitty.
His mom died.
I'm not talking about his mother dying.
I'm talking about you pulling this shit with your friend.
And I just don't want you to get involved in something
that will most definitely hurt you.
Addison Schacht, please report to the Principal's office.
Addison Schacht to the Principal's office.
That's it, Addison. Last chance.
What happened?
They're suspending me for a week.
What?
Because they looked in my locker for posters and they found Kevin's file.
Okay. Well, what are you going to do about it?
Now I've got nothing to lose.
Addison, they didn't expel you, okay?
Just go home and... And chill out.
They might not put it on your record.
A suspect was arrested on Thursday
in connection to a separate robbery.
Sunday morning at 4:30,
violence was unleashed downtown on a taxi driver.
In other news tonight,
police are still looking for leads
in the case of slain Kennedy High School student Kevin Broadus,
whose killer fled the scene on a red Honda motorcycle.
-Hi. -Hi.
Um, is Addison home?
No. Well, he should be, but no, he's not.
Phoebe?
-Yeah. -Oh!
-Hi. -Hi.
Well, why don't you come in? Yeah, yeah.
Come on in.
Yeah, okay. Um...
Don't mind me. It's chili night, and things tend to get out of control.
Oh, it's fine. Don't worry about it.
So, how are you doing?
Um...
I'm okay. You know, considering everything.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Do you want to sit down? Yeah.
-Sure. I don't mind standing, though, it's... -Here.
No...
Some of this stuff out of the way here.
Don't mind the mess.
It's okay.
How's your mom?
-You've known her for a while, right? -Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, since... Well, since she first came to Washington.
That's almost 20 years now.
Was she always so...
I don't know, like that?
Your mom's a perfectionist.
But she's had to work real hard to get where she's at,
and you seem to be turning out pretty good.
How do you think Addy's doing?
I don't know actually.
You know, I hope he's okay.
Addy?
-Hey, Dad. -Hey.
I saved some chili.
Uh, I'm not really hungry. I'm just gonna go to my room.
Hi, Addy.
What are you doing here?
Oh, we're just having some ice cream. Want some?
Just waiting on you.
Addison, come on!
Hey!
Addison?
Can I come in?
You have a nice little chat about me with my dad?
Come on, Addison.
Look, I'm just worried about you.
Well, if you came here to try to talk me out of doing anything crazy,
-don't bother. -That's not why I'm here.
I just came back from the police station.
And it was a complete waste of time.
I'm kidding myself.
No one's gonna solve this case,
and there's sure as shit nothing I can do about it.
All right. I heard something.
And I don't know if it's true or not,
but I've thought about it and I can't not tell you.
-What? -You can't overreact, all right?
Because I don't even know if it means anything yet.
I'm just giving you the information.
Yeah, what is it?
The guy was white.
The guy who killed Kevin.
Bo saw him. He said he was white.
What do you think, it was a race thing?
I don't know. Honestly, I don't think so.
Bo said that Kevin was hanging around with some pretty dangerous people.
Who?
Do you remember that kid Noel?
Fat Noel from eighth grade?
Yeah. That's who Kevin was hanging around with.
Phoebe, just because Noel listened to gangster rap when we were younger
doesn't make him dangerous.
All right, Addison. Well, look, that's what Bo told me.
He said Kevin was mixed up with some pretty heavy people.
So there. I told you.
Wait, hold on. Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Um, do you have Noel's number?
Why would I have Noel's number?
I don't... I don't know.
Do you think, um... Do you think Noel still has a Facebook?
Okay, so it's Tuesday night, around 11:15.
We're on our way to see our old friend Noel.
Earlier tonight, Phoebe told me that he might know something
about what happened to Kevin.
So, he invited us to this address, 267 Otis Street.
Um, this is... This is Otis Street here.
Wait, who are these guys? Maybe this is it.
I don't think this is it.
Oh, no, no, no. We're good. We're good.
Addison, this is super sketchy.
If they see that we're, you know, stressed out,
they're gonna think it's weird.
Just, you know, stay calm.
-Shit! Shit! Shit! -Go! Go!
Oh, my God!
Why the hell are we down here?
Just give me the address. What's the address again?
Addison, why are you turning...
No, that's it. That should be it.
There? That's an alleyway.
Relax, okay? It's gonna be fine.
I'm not gonna relax.
It's gonna be fine. We know him.
-We don't know Noel. -Yes, we do!
We went to school with him for so long!
-You saw Noel five years ago. -Five, so what?
-Five years ago. -Do you see where we are right now?
Fine. You can wait in the car then.
No way. I'm not doing that.
Is this really where Noel's friend lives?
What's his name again?
He said to ask for some guy named D. Cash.
Yo, you got visitors.
Come on in.
Take your hands out your pockets, man. You're making me nervous.
-So, you're Addison. -Yeah.
-I'm D. -Hey, man. Good to meet you.
What's your name, baby? Who is this?
You brought me a little gift right here?
I'm Phoebe.
-Phoebe. -Yeah.
-You want to have some fun? -I'm okay.
She's with me, man.
Mmm?
-I'm okay. -What'd you say?
She's... She's with me.
Man, I will slap your nose off your face, man.
Shut up, Addison.
Yeah, you heard her. You better shut up, dude.
All right.
Hey, your friend's here.
Noel, wake up, man.
Hey, get your ass up, Noel. They're here. Wake up.
Is that Noel?
Who's this bitch?
Hey man, it's Addison.
Addison, yeah. Good to see you, man.
You look like shit.
Well, sit down, man.
Uh, so, how you been, man?
You high already man. I'll take this. Put that shit down.
It's crazy, right?
It's been, like, five years, six years.
Why are you so interested all of a sudden?
Well, um, the reason why I'm here
is because I wanted to ask you about something.
-Okay. Uh... -Uh...
The shooting in Northwest at Seven Stars.
I don't know if you know or not, but this kid Kevin Broadus,
who we know, he was the one who got killed.
Yeah, what are you asking me for?
Well, I... I heard, you know, you guys were hanging out.
So, what do you think happened?
I mean, we just heard that the guy who did it was white...
Enough of this shit, man.
Enough.
Noel, you got this kid's number?
No.
I have a pager.
You got a pager.
Where you live, son?
Uh, we're actually from Philadelphia.
We're just visiting.
I know where he lives. You're still at the same place, right, Addy?
Yeah. Same place.
Good. I think you kids better get going, man. Get out of here.
No problem.
If we hear something, who knows?
Maybe we'll give you a call.
All right, white boy?
Okay. Thank you. I'll send him my number.
Get your ass home, man.
Why the hell would you tell them where you live?
Noel still thinks we live in Chevy Chase.
We used to be rich, remember?
Well, that's just great.
Phoebe. I'm really sorry.
-I don't want to hear it from you. -Okay? I... I am.
-I don't want to hear it! -Okay.
I need a break.
I can't keep doing this.
I can't be a part of this anymore.
Yeah, hello. Who is this?
Oh, yeah. Yes. This is he.
Yeah, no.
Thank you, sir, for calling.
Yes.
Okay.
Okay. I'll see you then.
Phoebe! Hi. I'm in here.
Listen, I'm hanging up, all right? Call me if you start to panic.
Bye.
-Good morning. -Hey.
Can we talk for a minute?
We can talk later. I gotta go.
It'll only take a minute.
Okay.
Well,
Addison Schacht's father called me last night.
Yeah?
It was kind of illuminating.
I have to admit. I didn't...
I hated the fact that he knows
more about what my own daughter is doing than I do.
Did you like it over there?
I mean, yeah.
I don't know, Mom. It was... It was fine.
Theo's a nice guy.
Yeah, he's a nice person.
It's true.
-Okay, well... -I just want to say that I'm... I'm...
What?
What I want to say is I apologize. I'm very sorry
for not listening to you.
Sincerely, my intention was to help.
I'm gonna head out. I love you, Mom. I gotta go.
I love you, too.
Okay.
Here we are.
Uh, 775 McKinley.
Kevin's house.
Uh...
Hi, Mr. Broadus.
You must be Addison.
Come inside.
Would you like something to drink?
I'm okay. Thank you.
So,
you're a friend of Kevin's?
Yeah, I'd definitely say we were friends.
Enough of a friend to go to all this trouble?
Sorry to be blunt, but the fact is we'd like to know
why you're taking such an interest.
Do you think the police aren't doing their job?
-But... -Then why are you so interested?
Well, I...
I guess it just doesn't really make any sense why anyone would want to kill Kevin.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. It's my dad. I'll turn it off.
Walter?
Come with me.
Walter.
My son valued his privacy.
He kept us out of here for the last year.
We had to break the locks.
Then when my wife could finally face coming in here...
She had to find this.
Open it.
Open it!
What is this?
You want a reason?
-There's your reason. -What is that?
-Look at me! -I don't know what that is!
-Why do you have a pager? -What?
-Are you a dealer? -No.
Were you supplying my son?
-No. Absolutely not! -Tell me!
Walter, stop!
Please.
Stop! Please!
What do you want from us, Addison?
You want to know why my son was killed?
I don't know why.
But maybe we're just going to have to learn to live with that.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to make it worse.
-Ni hao. -Ni hao.
Uh, Phoebe's been... Has early acceptance into Yale next year.
Um, excuse me.
-Hi. -Hey.
-Hi. What's going on? -I need to talk to you.
-Addy, this is a really bad time. -I need to talk to you.
Shit. Okay, just come on.
Addy, what? What's up?
I just came back from Kevin's house.
You know he was into drugs? Like, serious drugs?
-Wait, what? -Yeah.
I don't know. Maybe that's what Strauss meant by "emotional difficulties."
Phoebe.
Uh, hey.
I'm sorry, Mom. Just one second.
-Addy, I gotta go. I... -Wait. I just...
Phoebe! Please.
Addy, what is it?
You know, I never told you what happened that day with my mom.
No.
She was fine.
Nothing was wrong with her.
That morning, we were having breakfast,
and then I went to school, and when I came back she was...
It's okay.
She was still sitting in the same seat where I left her.
At the hospital, they told us that she'd had an aneurysm.
Then,
last week, we see Kevin at the coffee shop.
-He gave us our coffee. -Addison.
He gave me back my book.
It's not the same thing.
Yes. It is.
It is the same thing.
He was fine, too.
Don't you understand, Phoebe?
I couldn't do anything about her.
Addison.
I don't know. Maybe I'm trying to solve something that can't be solved.
Addison. Uh...
Man, give me the damn phone.
Yo, it's D.
We got something you might want to know, man.
Meet us in an hour.
Hey. No alcohol for minors.
No, we're good. Kid's with me.
So, where's the girl at?
You said you got something for me?
We got something for you. It's right here.
Just little errands, man. No big deal.
Look, you do this for us, you get a name. That simple.
Are you kidding me? I'm not... I'm not gonna do that.
Do I look like I'm kidding, hmm?
Hmm? Okay, well, you don't want to know nothing, man. I'm out of here.
Go back.
Hold on.
Thatta boy. Yeah.
Now we talking.
You're saying if I do this for you,
you're going to tell me who killed Kevin Broadus?
No.
But I will tell you the guy who knows the guy who did it.
Okay. And...
Where do I have to take it?
Back to your neighborhood.
We can't go down there, man.
Not in Chevy.
Police would be on our ass so tough. Sniff us out.
But a kid like you?
Golden.
Yeah, and crispy.
No. I'm gonna need a little more info.
I told you. I told you. Addy's a quick learner, man.
He's a quick learner. He ain't even got hair on his nuts.
Look at him.
Give him... Give him a taste.
Give him a taste. Okay. Let me tell you.
There's a guy, you know. He comes down, hangs out sometimes.
Smack dealer from Maryland.
He's out of his mind. He's...
You know, he comes into D.C. and he parties at the clubs.
-That's what he likes to do. -Yeah.
And according to our friend, Kevin was down there to buy some shit.
So dealer was sitting in his big chair, you know.
He's sitting in the room with all his homies at a table.
You know, he see Kevin. He decides to pick on him a little bit.
Nothing too serious.
The next thing you know, Kevin went right back at the guy,
and shit, man. Like he was going back and forth.
It made the guy look bad.
Bad. Real bad.
This kid disrespected the wrong guy.
Disrespected him, man. I don't even know what Kevin said,
but he said something because he got a big laugh.
I mean, he... He signed his own death warrant. Shit.
When... When was this?
A couple of days before he got shot.
You're saying that all he did
was say the wrong thing to the wrong guy?
Wrong damn thing, man.
Oh, my God.
Addison?
Alex?
-Uh... -What the hell are you doing here?
Is this 27... I think I have the...
Shit. Really?
Alex, who is it?
Uh, okay. Okay. Um...
Just act normal like I left my sports bag at school
and you're dropping it off as a favor.
This for you?
Just give it to me for God's sake.
All right. Thank you. Bye!
No, you're funny. Get the hell out of here. Go. All right.
See you later!
Hey, D. I did it. What's the name?
What name? What are you talking about, man?
Come on, D. What's the name? We had a deal.
Don't rush me, man.
Now, the guy we told you about, his name is Mike.
Mike Lorriner.
He was there when Kevin got into it with that dealer.
And what's the address?
-Hey. -Phoebe! Phoebe. Mike Lorriner.
Write this down, okay? Mike Lorriner. 9756 Fork Lute Road.
This is the guy who knows who did it. D. just told me.
Okay. So you already called the police, right?
No, no, no. It's fine. I'm just gonna go talk to him.
Addison, don't be stupid. Do not go there.
Just give the police the address and let them go.
-Phoebe, I got it covered. -Addison!
Hey.
Uh, hi. Are you Mike Lorriner?
-Who are you? -Um...
I'm sorry. I don't mean to bother you, but...
I heard that you knew something about what happened in D.C.
a few days ago.
You know, the kid who got shot at the coffee shop.
D.C.? I don't know anything, man.
It's about Kevin Broadus.
Uh, he was a friend of mine.
I don't know what you're talking about, man. Get out of here.
I heard that he pissed off a drug dealer or something, and you...
Do you know the guy?
I don't know, I just... I just... What did I just say to you?
Did you hear me?
I... I said, I... I... I don't know nothing.
-All right? Now... Now just get... -All right.
Get off my property.
Okay. Sorry, man. I'll go. I'm leaving.
Hey, wait, wait, wait. Wait. Who... Who gave you my name?
Who... Who told you to come here?
I'm sorry. It's just a mistake, okay?
Of course it was a mistake.
Who told you?
Uh...
This guy I know, D. Cash. He just... He said that you were there when...
D. Cash? D. Cash gave you my name?
Yeah.
Okay.
Uh...
Okay. Well, you... You... You tell D. Cash
that he probably shouldn't be running his mouth.
-You got it? -Okay.
I'm gonna just go now. Okay?
Whoa, what... What is that?
What is that light?
Are you... are you filming this?
My man. Are we making a movie?
Well, I... I guess I'm ready for my close-up.
Look, man.
If you don't know anything, it's fine. I can just leave.
Do you think I will not use this?
Bang!
That was pretty good, huh?
You don't even know who that dealer was, do you?
The one your boy Kevin pissed off.
That was D., you idiot.
Oh, he played you.
See, now I'm in a spot.
Uh, you know, I... I...
I did that ungrateful asshole a favor.
And this is the thanks I get?
Well, fuck the both of you.
Why is that? Well, question seven on the application asks you
to tell them what your best and worst qualities are,
but they only give you three-and-a-half inches.
Three-and-a-half inches on a page.
I'm sorry, but my worst qualities took up a lot more
than three-and-a-half inches.
So I decided to write a few extra pages.
How many?
-Twenty-two to be exact. -Wow!
-I realize that might seem a bit excessive. -It does.
However, how are you expected
to express the very essence of your being
and your views on how insanely crazy this world is
in such a tiny space on a page?
He's fine.
-He's very drowsy, but he's stable. -Okay.
Yeah, he's going to be all right.
Well...
Hi. Sorry. He's asking for Phoebe.
Okay.
Hmm.
You want some coffee or something?
Coffee? No.
Phoebe's here.
Thank you.
Hi.
You smell nice.
Did they find Lorriner?
Yeah.
They caught him. Somewhere in Virginia.
He still had the gun on him, Addy.
They think it's the same gun he used to kill Kevin.
And they got D. Cash and Noel, too.
The Broaduses know.
They know who killed their son.
You talked to them?
Yeah, they came by.
They left that letter for you.
I'm still so mad at you.
I know.
I should thank you.
Why?
Because if it weren't for you, I'd probably be dead.
Really? Because I totally thought you had it covered.
Video Diary, day...
I don't even know what day it is anymore.
But guess what?
Someone must have read those extra 22 pages
because I got into Chicago.
You know,
these past few months I've come to realize
that I don't have to pretend to be okay anymore.
Because for the first time in a long time,
I am really excited about the future.
?Amazing grace, how sweet...
But at the same time, it's never easy to say goodbye.
?That saved a wretch like me
?I once was lost
?But now... ?/i>
Well, I'm...
I'm glad we could stay for that.
Yeah.
I can't believe we're leaving for college already.
How do you feel?
Well, you know, I just... I feel weird, I guess.
What are your plans for the holidays?
You think you'll be back?
I don't know.
-I'll... I'll walk you to the door. -Okay.
-So... I guess... -Listen.
I... I got you something.
Maybe you can use it.